<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NovelKomik</string>
    <string name="detail_a">A Sky God’s Spiritual Foundation. It was the greatest natural treasure in all of existence, but the sacrifices one must make to gain the approval of such an entity was unimaginable.
        Ryu is a genius amongst geniuses.
        He was born with the four Grand Ancestral Bloodlines. The Lightning Qilin. The Fire Dragon. The Ice Phoenix. The Fire Phoenix…
        He was blessed with an Ancestral Grade Bone Structure and Ancestral Grade Meridians. The Ice Jade Crystal Bones. The Chaotic Silk Meridians…
        He was bestowed the First Ranked Heavenly Pupils. The Mysteries of Heaven and Earth Pupils…
        However, none of it mattered. Born with a False Spiritual Foundation, it seemed that all of his talent would go to waste. Unless…
        Unless he was willing to grasp his Fate in his own hands.
    </string>
    <string name="detail_b">The Third Dimension is collapsing. The Fourth Dimension is descending.
        First it seemed that only technology would evolve, but who knew the world itself could too? It wasn’t as simple as climate change or tectonic movement. No, the fundamental laws of physics that governed everything were changing.
        Leonel was fairly lucky. His family was decently well off, his father loved him enough to brew vomit inducing nutrient rich smoothies every morning, and this was both the day of the National Championship and his 521st confession to his dream girl, Aina. As his father always said, nothing was more important than respect and persistence.
        Unfortunately, everything changed that night. At the after party of ages, the world reached a saturation point and an apocalypse descended.
        Abilities awakened. Sub-Dimensional Zones opened. Invalids rampaged through the Earth like a virus
        Those who could evolve would have a slim chance for survival. Those who couldn’t would die.
    </string>
    <string name="detail_c">The 13th generation disciple of the Great Mount Hua Sect. One of the Three Great Swordsmen. The Plum Blossom Sword Saint, Chung Myung.
        After slicing the head of the peerless Heavenly Demon, who threw the world into chaos, he slept an eternal sleep on the peak of the Hundred Thousand Great Mountains. Jumping over a hundred years, he comes back in the body of a child.
        But… what? Mount Hua declined? What the hell are you talking about!?
        It’s only natural to want to live if you’re going broke.
        “Decline? Even though I’m here? Who would dare!”
        Plum blossoms eventually fall.
        But when the cold winter passes and spring comes, plum blossoms shall bloom again.
        “But I’m gonna die first before Mount Hua gets revived! If you’re gonna go bust, might as well do it right, you bastards!”
        The beginning of the Plum Blossom Sword Saint, Chung Myung’s solitary struggle to save the thoroughly declining Mount Hua Sect.
    </string>
    <string name="detail_d">He’s in the deepest part of Jianghu.
        Keep your eyes wide open.
        If you do not wish to get dragged into the abyss.
    </string>
    <string name="detail_e">5 years after the world changed, the final boss appeared. [The final boss for area Earth, the Frost Queen, has appeared.]
        The final boss! If we can just defeat her, our lives will go back to normal. The top five players in the world, including Specter Seo Jun-ho, finally defeated the Frost Queen… But they fell into a deep slumber. And then 25 years passed… “A second floor?
        It didn’t end when the Frost Queen died?” Specter awakes from his slumber.</string>
    <string name="detail_f">I want to kill invaders and live a happy daily life in a special world.
        Can’t I just ask for that?
        Why? Why can’t I do that?
        People say chasing two different rabbits will make you miss both, but…
        just don’t miss them
    </string>
    <string name="detail_g">Minjun Kim, an ordinary high school senior in Korea, was suddenly summoned to another world, where he became a dark mage.
        Determined to return home, he overcame all sorts of hardships and saved the other world with black magic before leaving all his wealth and glory as a hero behind to return to Earth. However, before he could fully enjoy his life, a problem arose.
        A dungeon break had occured and monsters came pouring out, threatening his comfortable days. Therefore, Minjun, who had just returned to earth, had no choice but to… enlist on the very next day!!!
    </string>
    <string name="detail_h">If the Grim Reaper calls your name three times, you will be taken to the underworld.
“Hyeokyeon Mugang.”
“Hyeokyeon Mugang.”
“Hyeokyeon Mu…”
You little shit! I want to live longer! Get out of here!
I desperately swallowed the Herb of Immortality, and to my surprise, I actually lived! When I finally opened my eyes, thinking it was all a dream… I was surrounded by a bunch of old guys?! I asked where am, and—the Shamans’ Mountain?!!!!!!!!
Somehow, I possessed the body of a pitiful errand boy… this is nuts!
I… I am… I am the strongest of the strong, the head of the Sa Clan, Hyeokyeon Mugang!!! Why am I now part of a clan of Shamans?!
Well, since I’m here, I might as well become the best disciple I can. The trashy master’s ruthless, no-holds-barred, immortal martial arts story “Path of the Shaman” begins!
    </string>
    <string name="detail_i">Seo MoonYeob was the world’s greatest superhuman, who sacrificed himself after saving humanity.
Thought to have been dead, he returns 17 years later to a now-peaceful world,
and the superhuman sport faces seismic change.
The story of a modern-fantasy sports-action starts now!
    </string>
    <string name="detail_j">The plot of TBATE is centered on King Grey, a mighty leader who is reincarnated into the continent of Dicathen as Arthur Leywin. However, Arthur did not reincarnate into a new world naked, without any skill his previous experience as a warrior helped him hone his skills as a mage faster than normal.</string>
    <string name="detail_k">When I opened my eyes, I was inside a novel.
[The Birth of a Hero].
[The Birth of a Hero] was a novel focused on the adventures of the main character, Choi Han, a high school boy who was transported to a different dimension from Earth, along with the birth of the numerous heroes of the continent.
I became a part of that novel as the tr*sh of the Count’s family, the family that oversaw the territory where the first village that Choi Han visits is located.
    </string>
    <string name="detail_l">Cursed his whole life with only misfortune and hardships, Cheon Yeo Woon, who ranks lowest in the war of the Grand Prince Succession is about to have his world turned upside own when a descendant from a future suddenley appears and installs nano machines inside his body
    </string>
    <string name="detail_m">Felix Maxwell was destined to be a loser, born on one of the weakest races and on the least favorable of situations, he was forced to face adversity head-on as he traveled across the vast universe where dangers laid in every corner, one day traveling in hopes of riches he stumbled upon a ruin where a supreme being laid imprisoned, in a stroke of bad luck the being laid its eyes on him and tried to take over his body, forcing itself upon him.
    </string>
    <string name="detail_n">Jin Runcandel was the youngest son of Runcandel, the land’s most prestigious swordsman family…
And the biggest failure in Runcandel history.
He, who was kicked out miserably and came to a meaningless end, was given another chance.
“How do you want to use this power?”
“I want to use it for myself.”
Memories of his past life, overwhelming talent, and a contract with God…
The preparations to become the greatest are complete.
    </string>
    <string name="detail_o">Lu Zhou wakes up to become the worlds most powerful and oldest villainous Patriarch, and finds that he has nine notorious disciples who are full of evil. His eldest disciple is the leader of the Nether Sect with thousands of minions, and his second disciple—Sword Devil—always slaughters others at the slightest disagreement...
Without his cultivation base, how will he handle these evil disciples?
His eldest disciple, Yu Zhenghai, said, "I've never had a rival in my life, and no one but Master can make me bow my head."</string>

</resources>